Muhammad Waleed Bin Tariq

Pakistan



muh.wbt@gmail.com

+923347111446



https://www.linkedin.com/in/muhammad-waleed-807636217

Summary

I am a Dot Net developer and a React developer. I have experience working as a freelancer in different projects. I develop good quality and responsive web pages. As a developer, I make modular, clean, object-oriented, and well-commented code, always aiming for quality and intelligence in the solutions. My solutions are complete, front-end.

I have experience with:

- √ C-Sharp
- √ Dot Net
- √ React JS
- √ Next JS
- √ Jet Brains IDE
- √ JavaScript | jQuery | React JS
- √ HTML/CSS

Experience

React JS Developer (Hybrid)

Data Majority

DEC 2022 - Present

This job role involves the frontend development. It is a very great experience working at Data Majority specifically in Lead role of Front-End taking on the challenges based on customer requirements/projects and delivering them on time and with utmost quality.

Font-end Developer

Freelance

JULY 2022 - SEP 2022

This job role involves the frontend development of an ecommerce website. It is a very great experience working at Data Majority specifically in Lead role of Front-End taking on the challenges based on customer requirements/projects and delivering them on time and with utmost quality.

Education



Comsats University Islamabad

BS(Computer Science)

2018 - 2022



Punjab Group of Colleges Rahim Yar Khan

Intermediate/Matric

2016 - 2018

Skills

• React JS • JavaScript • XML • Web Applications • HTML • Next JS • Angular • Dot Net • C-Sharp